Error 1 next retry ms= 1000 requests= 1
Error 2 next retry ms= 2000 requests= 2
Error 3 next retry ms= 4000 requests= 3
Error 4 next retry ms= 570000 requests= 4
Error 5 next retry ms= 570000 requests= 5
Error 6 next retry ms= 570000 requests= 6
Error 7 next retry ms= 570000 requests= 7
BUG exhausted retries: requests keep recurring at 570000 ms without any successful load.
BUG browser log: actual MonitorView error callback logs token-bearing event.url.
BUG same-camera race: older response overwrites newer URL; two timers remain.
BUG unmount: in-flight response schedules a new refresh timer after cleanup.
Dataset: fake HTTP/timers, extracted actual functions; 0 clips; not a browser integration test.
